CURTIS HODAK

7833 Farmsbury Dr. Reynoldsburg, Ohio · (740) 739-8189 Curtis.Hodak@icloud.com · <u>LinkedIn</u>

Experienced DevOps cloud engineer with solid release automation engineering, systems administration, and systems security experience. Self-motivated and able to learn new technologies, practices and procedures to ensure efficient delivery of secure infrastructure & software.

EXPERIENCE

FEBURARY 2019 – DECEMBER 2023

MOVEHQ, DEVOPS ENGINEER

- Imported legacy AWS infrastructure as IaC into Terraform codebase.
- Built and supported CI/CD automation, deployment, and continuous integration tools.
- Participated in engineering & QA scrum and design meetings to drive quality releases.
- Implemented monitoring processes, design/build/deploy monitoring dashboards.
- Enhanced infrastructure & application performance, security & APM systems
- Produced and maintained documentation on requirements, and procedures for systems.
- Drove downtime to near zero leveraging deployment automation.
- Participated in on-call rotations for DevOps escalations.

AUGUST 2015 - FEBURARY 2019

IGC SOFTWARE, QUALITY ASSURANCE ENGINEER

- Performed prerelease testing for various applications, and escalated issues to appropriate development teams for remediation.
- Initiated push to automated testing projects within the company.
- Tested out multiple frameworks for testing before deciding upon Ruby/Cucumber. This has since changed to a new framework.

JUNE 2015 – AUGUST 2015

IGC SOFTWARE, TECHNICAL SUPPORT ENGINEER

- Handled incoming calls to resolve desktop application, mobile application, paperwork, and pricing issues.
- Created tickets for developers to describe issues with replication steps so issues that were not able to be resolved by support could be released as developer fixes.

EDUCATION

JAN 2019 - PENDING

FRANKLIN UNIVERSITY

Completed various courses towards a bachelor's degree in computer science or cybersecurity.

MAY 2015

CENTRAL OHIO TECHNICAL COLLEGE, ASSOCIATE OF BUSINESS: IT & PROGRAMMING

Courses included: Multiple coding languages, computer hardware, website design, and many others.

MAY 2004

WATKINS MEMORIAL HIGHSCHOOL, HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

TECHNOLOGIES

- Gitlab / Github / Github actions
- AWS: VPC, EC2, RDS, EKS, S3, Route 53, etc.
- Terraform
- Docker / Docker Compose
- Kubernetes EKS, EKS + Fargate, Rancher, D2iQ
- Spacelift, Flux, Jenkins
- Octopus & TeamCity
- Elastic search / Kibana
- Datadog / Sumologic
- Prometheus / Grafana
- Ubuntu, CentOS, Amazon Linux, Windows Server

- Okta
- Jamf
- Atlassian Jira, Confluence
- GoDaddy / Network Solutions
- Wiz.io, AquaSec & Expel
- Python / Bash
- Ruby / Cucumber
- Java
- HTML/CSS
- SQL / MariaDB / MSSQL / Oracle DB

PERSONAL INTERESTS

- Playing and recording guitar. Released an album shortly after high school which was purchased and reviewed internationally as well as smaller projects and enjoying playing on personal time.
- Building and working with computer hardware. From building gaming PCs to troubleshooting other people's hardware problems. The latest technology is always exciting.
- Food, restaurants, dining, worked in bar and food service while pursuing my degree and enjoy preparing new recipes and exploring new types of food around town and during travel.